<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<android.support.v4.widget.DrawerLayout
    xmlns:android="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res/android"
    xmlns:app="http://schemas.android.com/apk/res-auto"
    android:layout_width="match_parent"
    android:fitsSystemWindows="true"
    android:layout_height="match_parent"
    android:id="@+id/drawerlayout1">



    <android.support.design.widget.CoordinatorLayout
        android:id="@+id/coordinatorlayout"
        android:layout_width="fill_parent"
        android:layout_height="match_parent"
        app:expandedTitleMarginStart="70dp">

        <android.support.design.widget.AppBarLayout
            android:theme="@style/ThemeOverlay.AppCompat.Dark.ActionBar"
            android:layout_width="fill_parent"
            android:layout_height="230dp"
            android:id="@+id/appBar">

            <android.support.design.widget.CollapsingToolbarLayout
                android:id="@+id/CollapsingToolbarLayout1"
                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                android:layout_height="match_parent"
                app:layout_scrollFlags="scroll|exitUntilCollapsed"
                android:background="#f5f5f5">

                <RelativeLayout
                    android:layout_width="match_parent"
                    android:layout_height="match_parent"
                    app:layout_collapseMode="parallax"
                    android:id="@+id/contenido2">

                    <ImageView
                        android:layout_width="match_parent"
                        android:layout_height="match_parent"
                        android:scaleType="fitCenter"
                        android:src="@drawable/faicheck"
                        android:id="@+id/portada"
                        android:layout_margin="16sp" />

                    <TextView
                        android:layout_width="wrap_content"
                        android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                        android:id="@+id/editText"
                        android:textColor="#575757"
                        android:fontFamily="sans-serif-light"
                        android:textSize="24sp"
                        android:text="Política de Privacidad"
                        android:layout_alignParentBottom="true"
                        android:layout_alignParentLeft="true"
                        android:layout_margin="26dp"
                        android:textStyle="bold" />

                    <RelativeLayout
                        android:layout_width="match_parent"
                        android:layout_height="3dp"
                        android:background="@drawable/gradiente"
                        android:layout_alignParentBottom="true"></RelativeLayout>

                </RelativeLayout>
                <android.support.v7.widget.Toolbar
                    android:id="@+id/toolbar1"
                    android:layout_width="match_parent"
                    android:layout_height="?attr/actionBarSize"
                    app:popupTheme="@style/ThemeOverlay.AppCompat.Light"
                    app:layout_collapseMode="pin"
                    app:titleTextAppearance="@style/Toolbar.TitleText"
                    android:minHeight="?attr/actionBarSize"/>

            </android.support.design.widget.CollapsingToolbarLayout>

        </android.support.design.widget.AppBarLayout>

        <android.support.v4.widget.NestedScrollView
            android:layout_width="match_parent"
            android:layout_height="match_parent"
            android:fillViewport="true"
            android:id="@+id/View"
            app:layout_behavior="@string/appbar_scrolling_view_behavior">




            <LinearLayout
                android:layout_width="fill_parent"
                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                android:orientation="vertical"
                android:background="#ebebeb">


                    <ScrollView
                        android:layout_width="match_parent"
                        android:layout_height="match_parent"
                        android:id="@+id/scrollView"
                        android:layout_margin="16sp">

                        <LinearLayout
                            android:orientation="vertical"
                            android:layout_width="match_parent"
                            android:layout_height="match_parent">

                            <TextView
                                android:layout_width="match_parent"
                                android:layout_height="wrap_content"
                                android:text="\n\nPrivacy Policy\n\n\nDavid Ricardo Araújo and Cristian Do Carmo built the Faicheck app as a open source app. This SERVICE is provided by us at no cost and is intended for use as is.\n\n\nThis page is used to inform website visitors regarding our policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use our Service.\n\n\nIf you choose to use our Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation with this policy. The Personal Information that We collect are used for providing and improving the Service. We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.\n\n\nThe terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, which is accessible at [App Name], unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy.\n\n///////////////////////////////////////////\n\n\nInformation Collection and Use\n\n\nFor a better experience while using our Service, We may require you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information, including but not limited to users name | password.  The information that We request is retained on your device and is not collected by us in any way.\n\n\nThe app does use third party services that may collect information used to identify you. [You can mention Google services here and link to Google&apos;s privacy policy if you want].\n\n\n///////////////////////////////////////////\n\n\nLog Data\n\n\nWe want to inform you that whenever you use our Service, in case of an error in the app We collect data and information (through third party products) on your phone called Log Data. This Log Data may include information such as your devices’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, device name, operating system version, configuration of the app when utilising our Service, the time and date of your use of the Service, and other statistics.\n\n\n///////////////////////////////////////////\n\n\nCookies\n\n\nCookies are files with small amount of data that is commonly used an anonymous unique identifier. These are sent to your browser from the website that you visit and are stored on your devices’s internal memory.\n\n\n///////////////////////////////////////////\n\n\nService Providers \n\n\nWe may employ third-party companies and individuals due to the following reasons:\n\n-To facilitate our Service;\n-To provide the Service on our behalf;\n-To perform Service-related services; or\n-To assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.\n\n\n\nWe want to inform users of this Service that these third parties have access to your Personal Information. The reason is to perform the tasks assigned to them on our behalf. However, they are obligated not to disclose or use the information for any other purpose.\n\n\n///////////////////////////////////////////\n\n\nSecurity\n\n\nWe value your trust in providing us your Personal Information, thus we are striving to use commercially acceptable means of protecting it. But remember that no method of transmission overthe internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and reliable, and We cannot guarantee its absolute security.\n\n\n///////////////////////////////////////////\n\n\nLinks to Other Sites\n\n\nThis Service may contain links to other sites. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that site. Note that these external sites are not operated by us. Therefore, I strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of these websites. I have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third-party sites or services.\n\n\n///////////////////////////////////////////\n\n\nChildren’s Privacy\n\n\nThis Services do not address anyone under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personal identifiable information from children under 13. In the case We discover that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information, We immediately delete this from our servers. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with personal information, please contact us so that We will be able to do necessary actions.\n\n\n///////////////////////////////////////////\n\n\nChanges to This Privacy Policy\n\n\nWe may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, you are advised to review this pageperiodically for any changes. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. These changes are effective immediately, after they are posted on this page.\n\n\n///////////////////////////////////////////\n\n\nContact Us\n\n\nIf you have any questions or suggestions about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us.\n"
                                android:id="@+id/textView3"
                                android:fontFamily="sans-serif-light"
                                android:textSize="18sp" />
                        </LinearLayout>
                    </ScrollView>



            </LinearLayout>



        </android.support.v4.widget.NestedScrollView>


        dScrollView>

    </android.support.design.widget.CoordinatorLayout>


</android.support.v4.widget.DrawerLayout>